[{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":0,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-05T18:41:48.297Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":0,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T18:41:48.100Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":0,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T18:41:35.853Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":0,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T18:41:33.095Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":0,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 19","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T18:41:29.249Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":0,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T18:41:29.198Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1493956671","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T04:58:56.675Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T04:31:51.272Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T04:31:50.059Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT15S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 08","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T04:31:48.780Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 08","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T04:31:33.065Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT414S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T04:28:10.761Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T04:21:16.696Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT423S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T04:11:03.195Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T04:04:00.190Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T04:03:58.809Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT11S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 09","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T04:03:53.642Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T04:03:55.084Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 09","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T04:03:42.479Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T03:58:49.738Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 5","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-05T03:58:43.065Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":3,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT30S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 3","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-05T03:58:30.155Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 3","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-05T03:58:00.629Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T03:58:00.197Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T03:57:51.765Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T03:57:51.756Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT150S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:18:35.789Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:16:05.686Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:16:05.584Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:16:02.935Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT159S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:16:01.355Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:13:22.049Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT108S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:12:27.771Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:10:39.913Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T03:10:39.720Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T03:10:37.552Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T03:10:34.323Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T03:10:33.149Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:10:28.696Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:10:31.887Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT76S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:07:45.113Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:29.226Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:29.126Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:28.824Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:28.499Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:28.018Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:27.920Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:27.458Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:27.367Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:26.871Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:26.735Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:26.182Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:26.090Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:25.487Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:25.335Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:24.560Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:24.380Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:23.200Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:23.095Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:22.526Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:22.432Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:21.800Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:21.702Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:21.096Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:21.000Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:20.375Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:20.286Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:19.648Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:19.552Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:18.737Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:18.643Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:06:16.690Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT377S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 09","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T03:05:48.952Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 09","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T02:59:31.649Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T02:59:31.537Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T02:59:30.370Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T02:59:30.274Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-05T02:59:28.204Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T02:59:28.108Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T02:59:24.525Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 12","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-05T02:59:20.790Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T02:59:20.776Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":4,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PEF_28","problem_set":"Final","time":"2017-05-05T02:16:17.856Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":4,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-05T02:16:17.793Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Winter 04 Problem 18","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-05-04T22:03:04.006Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T22:03:03.975Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":6,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T20:46:07.350Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":6,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T20:46:07.341Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1493925394","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T20:17:35.353Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":6,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T19:16:37.468Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":6,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T19:16:34.124Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":6,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T19:16:34.082Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":7,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W13 Problem 1E","problem_set":"10. ANOVA: Analysis of Variance","time":"2017-05-04T18:23:14.253Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":7,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T18:23:14.231Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Passive Filter Cutoff P1","problem_set":"Passive Filter Cutoff","time":"2017-05-04T17:18:21.168Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for EECS 314","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T17:18:19.991Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: EECS 314 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T17:18:12.915Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T17:18:11.254Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: EECS 314 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T17:18:09.077Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Decimal and Binary P1","problem_set":"Exam 3","time":"2017-05-04T17:18:06.467Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Active Filters P1","problem_set":"Exam 3","time":"2017-05-04T17:18:00.594Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for EECS 314","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T17:18:00.133Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: EECS 314 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T17:17:51.958Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Memory for Data P2","problem_set":"Exam 3","time":"2017-05-04T17:17:42.669Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for EECS 314","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T17:17:42.232Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: EECS 314 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T17:17:35.581Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T17:17:32.022Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":8,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T17:17:31.937Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":9,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T15:59:48.901Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":9,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T15:59:48.936Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT9S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 02","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:25:53.806Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 02","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:25:44.462Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT106S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:25:33.218Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:23:47.542Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT41S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 02","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:23:43.710Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 02","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:23:02.824Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT40S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:22:45.563Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:22:05.830Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT32S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 08","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:21:14.734Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 08","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:20:42.805Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT55S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:20:36.895Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:19:41.206Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT54S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 07","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:19:33.879Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 07","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:18:39.350Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT8S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:18:09.547Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:18:01.767Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT43S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2014 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 15","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:17:53.323Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2014 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 15","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:17:10.524Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:17:05.303Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:16:58.712Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT22S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:16:53.569Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:16:31.350Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT54S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 02","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:16:27.027Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 02","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:15:33.705Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT62S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:15:27.944Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:14:25.177Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:14:19.904Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:14:07.940Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT46S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 12","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:14:01.183Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 12","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:13:15.104Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT26S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 12","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:13:11.073Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 12","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:12:45.310Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT52S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 11","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:12:34.963Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 11","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:11:42.745Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT93S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 05","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:11:37.740Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 05","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:10:04.899Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT74S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:09:59.711Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:08:45.605Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT60S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:08:30.603Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:07:30.140Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT29S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:07:07.726Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:06:38.071Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT87S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 13","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:05:53.439Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 13","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:04:26.789Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT50S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 07","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:04:21.151Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 07","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:03:31.643Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":10,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT102S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:03:18.423Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-04T07:01:36.036Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T07:01:35.901Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T07:01:30.439Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T07:01:25.399Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":10,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T07:01:25.277Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1493864534","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T03:22:26.303Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T03:18:18.776Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 13","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:17.418Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:17.309Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:16.307Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:16.196Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:15.087Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 19","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:14.963Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 19","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:13.923Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:13.816Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:12.499Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:12.393Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:11.131Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:11.029Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:09.863Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:09.764Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:08.922Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:08.752Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:06.003Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 02","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:05.902Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 02","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:03.827Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:03.717Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:02.002Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 11","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:18:01.898Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 11","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:17:49.407Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT109S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 03","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:17:49.246Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 03","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:16:00.017Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT13S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 17","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:15:59.899Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 17","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:15:46.949Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 22","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:15:46.745Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 22","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:15:40.739Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T03:15:40.616Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T03:15:30.606Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:15:12.926Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT171S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:15:12.823Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:12:21.663Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:12:21.447Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:12:15.707Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:12:15.581Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T03:12:13.794Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT66S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T02:59:48.229Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Newton’s Laws","time":"2017-05-04T02:58:42.074Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T02:58:41.872Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T02:58:35.828Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:58:30.007Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:58:27.889Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:58:20.362Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT18S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:58:18.613Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:58:00.407Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:58:00.286Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:57:55.745Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT47S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:56:34.880Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:55:47.969Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT8S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:55:46.306Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:55:38.167Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:55:36.893Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:55:31.151Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT8S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:55:30.030Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:55:21.691Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 08","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:55:18.635Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 08","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-05-04T02:55:11.244Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T02:55:11.129Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T02:55:03.918Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 22","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-05-04T02:51:11.003Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT333S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-05-04T02:50:43.127Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-05-04T02:45:10.137Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T02:45:09.957Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T02:44:56.211Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-04T02:44:48.825Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T02:44:48.812Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T02:22:14.572Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T02:22:14.563Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1493854687","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-04T00:38:07.775Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:29.939Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:29.846Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:28.820Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 18","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:28.721Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 18","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:26.492Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:26.337Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:25.007Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:24.912Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:22.973Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:22.871Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:21.863Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:21.762Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:19.931Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:19.835Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:18.463Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:18.366Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:17.511Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:17.414Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:05.227Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:05.073Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:04.232Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:04.136Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:03.030Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:02.932Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:01.842Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:01.741Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:00.877Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:54:00.774Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:56.816Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:56.719Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:55.802Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:55.706Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:54.538Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:54.444Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:52.160Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:52.060Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:50.859Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:50.767Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:49.573Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:49.474Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:48.149Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:47.989Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:46.972Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:46.868Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:45.069Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT14S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:41.648Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:27.809Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:27.713Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:26.996Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:26.827Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:25.674Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:25.570Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:24.600Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:24.506Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:23.850Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:23.758Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:23.029Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:22.928Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:21.831Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:21.731Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:20.329Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:20.232Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:19.177Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 17","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:19.077Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 17","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:17.064Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:16.956Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:15.531Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT8S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:15.431Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:07.617Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:07.513Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:05.260Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:53:05.160Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:52:59.367Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT97S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:52:59.259Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:51:22.722Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:51:22.625Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:51:17.524Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:51:17.422Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:51:14.522Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:51:14.399Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:51:12.286Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT15S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:51:08.911Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:53.626Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:53.470Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:52.153Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:52.056Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:50.982Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:50.875Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:50.169Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:50.073Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:49.214Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:49.117Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:48.120Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:47.963Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:46.617Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:46.513Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:50:43.983Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T23:38:07.112Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T23:38:07.103Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1493838839","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T23:37:27.424Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT321S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:24:16.171Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:18:55.310Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:18:55.211Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:18:54.231Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:18:54.138Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:18:52.256Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT320S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:18:30.807Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:10.196Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:10.004Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:08.253Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:08.147Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:06.522Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:06.429Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:05.399Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:05.281Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:04.421Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:04.239Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:02.920Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:02.810Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:01.750Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:13:01.643Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:12:57.068Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:12:56.968Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:12:56.189Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:12:56.094Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:12:54.938Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:12:54.846Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:12:49.480Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:12:49.382Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:12:45.974Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT58S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:12:41.009Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:42.595Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:42.403Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:40.003Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:39.875Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:38.727Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:38.608Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:37.647Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:37.555Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:36.412Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:36.286Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:35.449Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:35.343Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:31.643Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:31.544Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:30.530Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:30.433Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:29.470Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:29.366Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:28.337Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:28.242Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:27.063Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:26.960Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:11:21.722Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT254S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:10:31.803Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:17.049Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:16.951Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:15.424Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:15.321Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:14.304Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:14.195Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:13.014Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:12.909Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:11.672Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:11.571Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:10.097Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:09.990Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:08.662Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT160S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:06:08.562Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:03:28.782Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:03:28.676Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:03:27.217Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT40S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:03:27.111Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:47.143Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:46.976Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:45.928Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:45.826Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:44.409Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:44.311Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:42.994Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:42.878Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:36.901Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:35.628Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:30.470Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 18","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:30.368Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 18","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:28.808Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:28.713Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:25.757Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:25.573Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:23.301Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:23.203Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:21.504Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:21.399Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:20.374Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:20.270Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:16.895Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT28S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:02:15.147Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:47.275Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:47.175Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:46.233Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:46.133Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:45.069Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:44.975Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:43.595Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:43.429Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:42.363Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:42.258Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:40.993Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:40.894Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:39.669Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:39.567Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:38.493Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:38.346Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:36.239Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:36.141Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:35.113Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:35.013Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T23:01:31.744Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T23:01:31.572Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T23:01:28.668Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T23:01:28.659Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1493831503","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T23:01:26.154Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:10:06.828Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:10:06.731Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:10:04.682Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT11S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:10:04.583Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:09:53.589Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:09:52.548Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:09:47.428Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT296S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:07:30.442Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:34.157Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:34.051Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:33.532Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:33.332Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:32.680Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:32.583Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:31.750Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:31.654Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:28.664Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:28.569Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:26.690Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:26.594Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:23.683Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:23.588Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:22.005Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:21.907Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:17.596Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT20S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:02:16.177Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:56.262Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:56.142Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:55.068Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:54.958Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:53.112Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:53.015Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:51.901Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:51.787Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:50.974Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:50.873Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:49.840Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:49.744Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:48.297Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:48.180Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:45.948Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:45.791Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:43.484Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT28S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:43.390Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:01:15.173Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT26S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:00:36.817Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:00:10.331Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:00:10.235Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:00:06.985Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:00:06.880Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:00:03.685Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T21:00:03.552Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:59:51.685Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT31S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:58:44.118Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:58:13.276Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:58:13.177Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:58:09.680Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT45S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:58:07.594Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:57:22.851Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT66S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:57:09.719Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":12,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:56:14.713Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":12,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:56:10.060Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":12,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:56:10.051Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:56:03.303Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:56:03.118Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:56:00.827Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT28S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:55:59.706Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":13,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:55:55.910Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":13,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:55:55.902Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":14,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:55:52.299Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":14,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:55:44.117Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":14,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:55:44.111Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":15,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:55:43.711Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":15,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:55:39.204Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":15,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:55:39.198Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:55:31.219Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT16S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:55:31.112Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:55:15.972Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:55:14.387Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:55:10.657Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":16,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:54:24.803Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT35S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:54:20.977Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":16,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:54:18.358Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":16,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:54:18.349Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":17,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:53:47.564Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:45.319Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:45.133Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:44.392Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:44.293Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:43.705Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:43.556Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":18,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:53:43.442Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:42.678Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:42.572Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:41.927Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:41.829Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":17,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:53:41.076Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":17,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:53:41.071Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:40.576Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT14S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:40.456Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":18,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:53:37.511Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":18,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:53:37.506Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:26.347Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:26.243Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:25.312Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:25.203Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:24.251Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:24.142Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:23.002Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:22.895Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:21.146Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT10S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:21.037Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":19,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:53:13.266Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":19,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:53:13.249Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:53:11.905Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":20,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:53:07.397Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":20,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:53:07.388Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":21,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:47.140Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":22,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:41.486Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":22,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:39.049Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":22,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:39.045Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":23,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:38.723Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":24,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:36.441Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":25,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:35.496Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":24,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:33.478Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":24,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:33.472Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":26,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:31.392Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":25,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:31.059Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":25,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:31.041Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":23,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:30.974Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":23,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:30.968Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":21,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:27.950Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":26,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:24.561Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":26,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:24.553Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":27,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:21.405Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":21,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:21.046Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":21,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:21.041Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":27,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:15.577Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":27,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:15.567Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":28,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:09.644Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":28,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:52:09.636Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":29,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:51:54.726Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":28,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:51:50.362Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":29,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:51:48.833Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":29,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:51:48.826Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":28,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:51:47.126Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":28,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:51:47.118Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":30,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:51:40.243Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":30,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:51:38.398Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":30,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:51:37.287Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":30,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:51:29.151Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":31,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:50:47.038Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":30,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:50:40.768Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":30,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:50:40.759Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":31,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:50:37.104Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":31,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T20:50:37.097Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT193S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 08","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:50:20.361Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 08","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:47:07.459Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:47:07.357Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:47:05.750Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT41S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:47:03.716Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:46:22.214Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:46:22.111Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:46:21.086Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:46:20.952Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:46:18.249Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT198S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:42:46.107Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:39:28.683Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:39:28.555Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:39:27.503Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:39:27.402Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:39:24.874Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT212S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:38:50.463Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:18.151Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:18.044Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:16.648Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 18","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:16.518Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 18","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:15.696Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:15.584Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:14.647Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:14.535Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:13.323Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:13.131Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:11.382Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:11.277Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:10.270Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:10.157Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:09.062Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:08.961Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:08.137Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 17","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:08.020Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 17","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:35:06.309Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT183S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:34:36.605Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:33.670Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:33.502Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:32.124Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:32.025Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:30.923Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:30.736Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:29.430Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:29.332Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:28.145Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:28.005Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:26.858Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:26.762Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:25.436Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:25.340Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:31:20.118Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT73S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:30:18.692Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:29:05.736Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT26S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:28:43.817Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:28:17.327Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 17","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:28:17.234Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 17","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:28:16.431Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:28:16.325Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:28:15.353Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:28:15.258Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:28:13.852Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:28:13.757Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:28:06.250Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:28:03.017Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:58.652Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:58.467Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:56.547Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:56.454Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 2 Spring 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:55.167Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:55.034Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:51.115Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:51.019Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:47.036Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT29S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:39.976Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:10.792Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT8S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:09.537Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:00.998Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:27:00.901Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:26:58.509Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT255S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:26:18.361Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:22:03.144Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:22:03.028Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:22:00.172Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 08","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:22:00.075Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 08","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:59.572Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:59.448Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:59.133Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:58.892Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:57.804Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:57.703Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:56.716Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:56.615Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:55.912Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:55.811Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:54.627Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:54.531Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:53.099Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT121S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:21:53.005Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:19:51.914Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:19:51.805Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:19:49.901Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT284S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:19:23.913Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:14:39.458Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:14:39.363Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:14:34.873Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:14:34.779Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:14:31.261Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:14:31.168Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:14:26.076Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT197S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:11:56.007Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:38.141Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:38.045Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:37.096Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:37.004Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:36.104Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:35.989Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:34.995Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:34.886Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:33.727Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:33.636Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:28.471Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT123S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 08","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:08:17.586Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 08","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:06:14.709Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT20S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:05:55.934Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 04","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:05:35.623Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT8S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:05:35.527Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 13 Problem 21","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:05:27.881Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT38S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:05:05.093Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:04:27.473Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT58S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:03:45.349Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:47.066Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:46.967Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:43.451Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:43.353Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:40.647Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:40.547Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:35.732Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:35.627Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:33.607Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:33.445Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:32.083Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:31.981Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:30.961Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:30.867Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:29.958Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:29.866Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:27.180Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:27.079Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:22.633Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:22.481Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:18.773Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT27S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:02:16.896Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T20:01:49.801Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT408S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T19:37:12.890Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T19:30:24.757Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT14S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T19:29:44.281Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T19:29:30.749Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:21:53.585Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 W14 Problem 7A","problem_set":"5. Learning about a Population Proportion","time":"2017-05-03T19:21:51.903Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W13 Problem 12","problem_set":"5. Learning about a Population Proportion","time":"2017-05-03T19:21:43.531Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:21:41.788Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 W12 Problem 10A","problem_set":"5. Learning about a Population Proportion","time":"2017-05-03T19:21:40.049Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W12 Problem 4A","problem_set":"5. Learning about a Population Proportion","time":"2017-05-03T19:21:39.982Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W12 Problem 4A","problem_set":"5. Learning about a Population Proportion","time":"2017-05-03T19:21:37.383Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 F12 Problem 8B","problem_set":"5. Learning about a Population Proportion","time":"2017-05-03T19:21:37.318Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 F12 Problem 8B","problem_set":"5. Learning about a Population Proportion","time":"2017-05-03T19:21:35.577Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W13 Problem 10B","problem_set":"5. Learning about a Population Proportion","time":"2017-05-03T19:21:35.438Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W13 Problem 10B","problem_set":"5. Learning about a Population Proportion","time":"2017-05-03T19:21:30.561Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:21:30.469Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":33,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:15:14.637Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":34,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:15:08.827Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":33,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:15:07.155Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":33,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:15:07.150Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":34,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:15:05.783Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":34,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:15:05.778Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":35,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:14:53.688Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":35,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:14:51.354Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":35,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:14:42.523Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:14:04.294Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:13:59.698Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":32,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:13:59.690Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":36,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:13:38.092Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":37,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:13:34.513Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":36,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:13:28.117Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":36,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:13:28.112Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":37,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:13:08.348Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":37,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:13:02.846Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":37,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:13:02.838Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":38,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:12:34.449Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":39,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:12:30.914Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":39,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:12:21.367Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":39,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:12:21.363Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":38,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:12:07.286Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":38,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:12:02.364Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":38,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:12:02.356Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":40,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:12:00.345Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":41,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:11:52.746Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":40,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:11:48.776Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":40,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:11:48.762Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":41,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:11:44.095Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":41,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:11:44.083Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":42,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:10:45.775Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":42,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:10:45.770Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":43,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:10:36.733Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":43,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:10:34.471Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":43,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:10:24.791Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":43,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:10:24.784Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":44,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:10:03.003Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":44,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:53.257Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":44,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:50.423Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":44,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:40.896Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":44,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:40.888Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":45,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:40.417Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":46,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:40.278Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":46,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:34.240Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":46,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:34.235Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":47,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:25.031Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT30S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T19:09:24.450Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":45,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:22.539Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":47,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:22.049Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":47,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:22.041Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":45,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:18.181Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":45,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:09:18.176Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T19:08:54.586Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":48,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:08:43.857Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":48,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:08:36.162Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":49,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:08:32.647Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":48,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:08:32.560Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":48,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:08:32.551Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":49,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:08:27.294Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":49,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:08:27.287Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":50,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:07:33.424Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":50,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:07:27.723Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":50,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T19:07:27.719Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT105S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T18:59:28.305Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 09","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T18:57:43.662Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT124S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 18","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T18:57:20.602Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 18","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T18:55:16.003Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T18:55:15.907Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 15","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T18:55:13.673Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT97S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T18:55:13.576Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T18:53:36.962Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T18:53:36.859Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T18:53:31.777Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 18","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:53:29.618Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:53:29.520Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:53:27.240Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT115S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 4 Spring 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:50:21.135Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 4 Spring 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:26.317Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 4 Spring 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:26.226Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 4 Spring 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:24.218Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT10S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:24.125Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:14.789Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:14.685Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:13.750Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 18","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:13.651Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 18","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:12.118Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:12.028Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:11.280Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:11.182Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:09.940Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:09.847Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:08.930Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:08.838Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:06.788Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT15S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:48:05.275Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:47:50.481Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT141S","problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:41:45.466Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:39:24.618Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:39:24.522Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:39:19.205Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 18","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:39:19.113Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 18","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:39:16.713Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT28S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 20","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:39:16.619Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 20","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:38:48.480Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:38:48.386Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:38:44.204Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:38:44.110Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:38:41.714Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":35,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T18:37:37.379Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":35,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T18:37:34.538Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":35,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T18:37:31.044Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":35,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T18:37:31.039Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":51,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T18:36:50.402Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":51,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T18:36:45.407Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":51,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T18:36:45.080Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT547S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:35:09.036Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:26:02.621Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:26:02.524Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:26:00.070Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:25:59.968Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:25:58.595Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT165S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 4 Spring 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:25:58.502Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 4 Spring 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:23:13.348Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT364S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:23:01.975Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:16:57.696Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT22S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:16:55.860Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:16:33.047Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:16:32.943Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:16:26.625Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:16:26.531Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:16:24.281Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT23S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:16:24.181Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:16:01.075Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT14S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:16:00.959Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:15:46.578Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT29S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:14:48.813Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:14:19.377Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:14:19.284Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:14:07.739Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT18S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:14:07.642Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:13:49.004Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT573S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:11:06.125Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:01:33.785Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT395S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T18:01:33.682Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T17:54:58.459Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT368S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T17:53:15.451Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":52,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:50:09.101Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":52,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:50:09.095Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":53,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:49:52.489Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":53,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:49:52.484Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":54,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:47:10.252Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T17:47:07.307Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":54,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:47:07.047Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":54,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:47:07.042Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":55,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:47:04.918Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":55,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:55.577Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":55,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:55.572Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":56,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:14.662Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":56,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:14.657Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":57,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:11.494Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":58,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:10.476Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":57,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:08.996Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":57,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:08.986Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":59,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:06.764Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":58,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:06.015Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":58,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:06.010Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":60,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:04.084Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":60,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:00.492Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":60,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:00.486Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":59,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:00.328Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":59,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:46:00.323Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":61,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:51.666Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:48.919Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":61,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:48.689Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":61,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:48.684Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":63,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:46.876Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:44.691Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":63,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:42.563Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":63,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:42.558Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":64,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:40.973Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:37.182Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:37.171Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":64,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:37.114Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":64,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:37.107Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":65,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:01.859Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":66,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:45:00.722Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":65,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:44:59.577Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":65,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:44:59.565Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":67,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:44:56.483Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":66,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:44:56.463Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":66,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:44:56.454Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":67,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:44:52.745Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":67,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:44:52.736Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":68,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:44:03.296Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":69,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:44:03.105Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":70,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:44:02.057Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":70,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:56.562Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":70,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:56.557Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":68,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:56.311Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":68,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:56.306Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":71,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:55.201Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":72,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:53.669Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":71,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:51.898Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":71,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:51.892Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":72,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:50.290Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":72,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:50.285Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":73,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:49.311Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":73,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:49.301Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":69,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:48.729Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":69,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:48.724Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":74,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:32.499Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":74,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:27.370Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":74,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:43:27.364Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":75,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:40:54.052Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":75,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:40:54.040Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":76,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:39:56.693Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":76,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:39:56.683Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":77,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:38:52.097Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":77,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:38:47.133Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":77,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:38:47.125Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":78,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:37:54.146Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":78,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:37:51.208Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":78,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:37:43.574Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":78,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:37:43.448Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":78,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:37:17.918Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":78,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:37:17.908Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":79,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:52.522Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":80,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:45.418Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":79,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:45.073Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":79,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:44.136Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":79,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:42.724Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":80,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:41.649Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":80,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:41.645Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":79,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:40.997Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":79,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:38.991Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":79,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:34.505Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":81,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:29.693Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":82,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:28.463Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":82,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:26.777Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":79,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:25.634Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":79,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:25.629Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":81,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:23.213Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":81,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:23.198Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":82,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:19.858Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":82,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:19.849Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":83,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:14.926Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":84,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:13.905Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":84,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:11.586Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":85,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:09.875Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":83,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:09.272Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":83,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:09.267Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":84,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:06.861Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":85,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:04.502Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":85,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:04.497Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":84,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:02.731Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":84,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:02.721Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":86,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:01.762Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":86,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:36:00.191Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":86,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:35:51.284Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":87,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:35:45.394Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":87,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:35:45.388Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":86,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:35:44.446Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":86,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:35:44.442Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":88,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:35:37.893Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":88,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:35:30.975Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":88,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:35:30.968Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":89,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:58.980Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":89,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:54.738Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":90,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:54.025Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":91,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:51.143Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":92,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:50.526Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":93,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:50.298Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":93,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:50.290Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":90,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:49.988Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":90,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:49.983Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":89,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:49.238Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":89,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:49.229Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":91,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:45.873Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":91,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:45.851Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":92,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:41.197Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":92,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:32.620Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":92,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:33:32.612Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":94,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Thevenin Equivalent Resistance P4","problem_set":"Thevenin Equivalent Resistance","time":"2017-05-03T17:32:21.326Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":94,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for EECS 314","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:32:20.880Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":94,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: EECS 314 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:32:13.220Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":94,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:32:04.088Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":95,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:31:42.436Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":95,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:31:38.190Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":95,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:31:38.186Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":94,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 2 Winter 07 Problem 03","problem_set":"Magnetic force","time":"2017-05-03T17:31:04.286Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":94,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:31:04.247Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT333S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T17:17:16.719Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T17:11:43.910Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T17:11:43.887Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":96,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:48:30.908Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":97,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:48:30.637Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":96,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:48:25.394Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":96,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:48:25.390Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":97,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:48:24.817Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":97,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:48:24.808Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":98,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:46:50.572Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":99,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:46:17.413Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":99,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:46:12.621Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":99,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:46:12.617Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":100,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:46:09.585Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":100,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:46:03.079Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":100,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:46:03.071Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":101,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:45:53.139Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":98,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:45:50.758Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":98,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:45:50.753Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":102,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:45:50.427Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":101,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:45:48.150Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":101,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:45:48.145Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":102,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:45:43.495Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":102,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:45:43.490Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":103,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:58.099Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":104,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:49.137Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":105,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:48.335Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":103,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:46.986Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":103,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:46.977Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":105,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:44.310Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":105,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:44.305Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":104,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:43.442Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":104,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:43.435Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":106,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:43.195Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":106,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:35.662Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":106,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:35.657Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":107,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:13.066Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":107,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:04.518Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":107,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:44:04.514Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":108,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:43:53.914Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":108,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:43:49.812Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":108,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:43:49.803Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":109,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:43:22.403Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":109,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:43:13.997Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":109,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:43:13.990Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":110,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:43:07.975Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":110,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:43:03.838Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":110,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:43:03.830Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":111,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:43:00.064Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":111,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:42:55.497Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":111,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:42:55.489Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":112,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:42:45.272Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":113,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:42:45.140Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":112,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:42:41.000Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":112,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:42:40.995Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":113,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:42:40.736Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":113,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:42:40.723Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":114,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:42:17.784Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":114,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:42:13.019Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":114,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:42:13.011Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:34:28.134Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:34:24.180Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:34:19.470Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":11,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T16:34:14.622Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T16:34:11.474Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:34:10.520Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:34:05.428Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:34:02.943Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:33:58.942Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":11,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 12","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-05-03T16:33:55.023Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 12","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-05-03T16:33:52.017Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:33:51.894Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:33:41.971Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":11,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 14","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-05-03T16:33:37.550Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 14","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-05-03T16:33:34.756Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":11,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 09","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-05-03T16:33:28.749Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 09","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-05-03T16:33:25.419Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:33:25.267Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:33:20.895Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-05-03T16:33:18.814Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 17","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-05-03T16:33:15.222Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":11,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-05-03T16:33:09.224Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-05-03T16:32:57.494Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:32:57.340Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:32:44.497Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:32:41.111Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:32:35.898Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":11,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:32:35.887Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":115,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:29:10.912Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":115,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:29:08.410Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":116,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:29:03.768Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":115,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:29:02.813Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":115,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:29:02.805Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":117,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:53.207Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":117,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:49.419Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":117,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:49.413Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":118,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:47.030Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":119,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:40.677Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":116,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:37.934Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":116,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:37.928Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":120,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:34.693Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":119,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:27.543Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":121,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:26.000Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":121,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:21.515Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":121,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:21.497Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":120,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W12 Problem 7B","problem_set":"12. Chi-Square Tests","time":"2017-05-03T16:28:18.461Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":120,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:18.302Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":122,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:13.148Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":122,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:07.430Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":122,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:07.420Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":119,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:02.453Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":119,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:28:02.445Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":123,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:57.264Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":124,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:54.750Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":123,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:53.107Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":123,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:53.102Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":124,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:51.396Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":124,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:51.389Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":120,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:46.413Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":118,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:46.384Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":118,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:46.368Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":125,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:45.796Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":126,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:44.341Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":125,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:41.657Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":120,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:41.654Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":120,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:41.638Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":125,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:41.639Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":126,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:38.607Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":126,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:27:38.596Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":127,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:43.117Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":128,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:42.285Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":129,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:40.344Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":127,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:37.733Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":127,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:37.726Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":128,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:35.921Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":128,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:35.917Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":129,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:33.821Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":129,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:33.812Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":130,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:32.755Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":130,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:24.050Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":130,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:24.045Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":131,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:20.941Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":131,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:15.827Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":131,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:15.820Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":132,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:26:06.077Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":133,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:59.716Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":132,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:58.964Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":132,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:58.956Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":133,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:54.579Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":133,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:54.573Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":134,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:53.430Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":134,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:46.948Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":134,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:46.942Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":135,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:28.696Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":136,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:27.846Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":135,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:16.040Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":135,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:16.034Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":137,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:07.793Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":136,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:07.216Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":138,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:05.140Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":138,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:05.130Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":137,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:05.057Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":137,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:05.052Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":136,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:03.518Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":136,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T16:25:03.513Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":139,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB5_034","problem_set":"Gases","time":"2017-05-03T13:36:25.330Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":139,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT53S","problem":"PB5_038","problem_set":"Gases","time":"2017-05-03T13:36:18.311Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":139,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB5_038","problem_set":"Gases","time":"2017-05-03T13:35:25.013Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":139,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB5_004","problem_set":"Gases","time":"2017-05-03T13:34:19.103Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":139,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T13:34:17.611Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":139,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T13:34:05.986Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":139,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T13:34:02.868Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":139,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T13:33:58.021Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":139,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T13:33:57.517Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 19","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:41.010Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:40.857Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:39.009Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:38.904Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:38.038Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:37.949Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:37.274Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:37.172Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:36.493Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:36.399Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:35.694Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 18","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:35.595Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 18","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:34.926Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:34.800Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:34.186Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:34.090Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:33.264Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 4 Spring 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:33.167Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 4 Spring 11 Problem 05","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:26.880Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:26.782Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:25.882Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:25.785Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:25.155Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:25.062Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:24.413Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:24.320Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:23.123Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:23.027Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:22.377Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:22.284Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:21.696Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:21.601Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:20.790Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:20.702Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:18.103Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:17.947Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:15.822Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:15.720Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:14.289Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:14.193Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:13.559Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:13.469Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:12.702Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:12.608Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:11.872Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:11.780Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:11.169Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:11.073Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:10.282Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:10.186Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:04.422Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:04.331Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:03.433Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 10 Problem 08","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:03.335Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 10 Problem 08","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:35:00.940Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT124S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:34:36.693Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:32.607Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:32.508Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:31.853Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:31.758Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:31.092Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:31.002Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:30.242Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:30.080Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:29.114Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:29.022Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:28.219Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:28.125Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:27.481Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 11","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:27.384Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 11","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:26.608Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:26.517Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:25.712Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:25.618Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:24.494Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:24.347Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:32:22.368Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 2 Problem 6","problem_set":"Chapter 2","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:51.919Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 2 Problem 2","problem_set":"Chapter 2","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:51.561Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 2 Problem 2","problem_set":"Chapter 2","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:48.679Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 3","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:48.129Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 3","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:46.002Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 2 Problem 1","problem_set":"Chapter 2","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:45.520Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 2 Problem 1","problem_set":"Chapter 2","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:43.989Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 3","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:43.515Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 3","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:39.604Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 6","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:39.120Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 6","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:36.709Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 2 Problem 2","problem_set":"Chapter 2","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:36.229Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 2 Problem 2","problem_set":"Chapter 2","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:32.107Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 9","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:31.784Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 9","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:29.113Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 2 Problem 4","problem_set":"Chapter 2","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:28.802Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 2 Problem 4","problem_set":"Chapter 2","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:24.416Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 6","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:24.121Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT221S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:22.247Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 6","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-03T04:31:20.182Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T04:31:19.837Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:41.780Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:41.690Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:40.635Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:40.541Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:39.514Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:39.425Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:38.346Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:38.048Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:37.048Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:36.953Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:34.944Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:34.851Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:33.215Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT9S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:33.123Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:24.174Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:24.083Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:23.201Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:23.108Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:22.098Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:22.002Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:27:17.861Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT470S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:26:41.661Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 02","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T04:23:53.483Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":140,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT1272S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 05","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T04:23:49.369Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:18:51.123Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 19","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:18:51.022Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 19","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:18:49.913Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:18:49.813Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:18:48.935Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:18:48.835Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:18:47.043Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT203S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:18:12.053Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 13","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:49.403Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:49.307Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:47.753Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:47.632Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:44.963Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:44.867Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:44.005Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:43.911Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:42.719Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:42.623Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:37.692Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT281S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:14:13.909Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T04:12:33.606Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T04:12:33.598Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1493781085","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T04:11:29.383Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 11","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:09:32.798Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:09:32.693Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:09:30.630Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT53S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 04","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T04:02:36.838Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 05","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T04:02:37.179Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT151S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:02:33.297Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 04","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T04:01:43.020Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT9S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 05","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T04:01:42.867Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 05","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T04:01:33.671Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT10S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2014 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 06","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T04:01:33.436Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2014 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 06","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T04:01:23.064Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T04:01:22.911Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T04:01:19.316Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:00:02.838Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 20","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T04:00:02.694Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 20","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:59:57.784Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT70S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 12 Problem 24","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:59:01.000Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":140,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT24S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T03:58:32.591Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T03:58:08.352Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":140,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT27S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 10","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:55.701Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 12 Problem 24","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:50.469Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 20","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:50.373Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 20","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:49.004Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:48.916Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:47.963Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:47.870Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:46.893Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:46.795Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:42.013Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:41.916Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:40.713Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:40.606Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:39.230Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:39.128Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 10","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:32.567Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:32.474Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:30.721Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:30.625Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 10","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:28.360Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT26S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:28.168Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:28.145Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:28.043Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:25.442Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:25.345Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:23.209Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:23.113Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:21.609Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:21.499Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 09","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:19.080Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:18.985Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:16.677Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT12S","problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:16.574Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:04.002Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:03.899Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:02.134Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:01.987Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:57:00.085Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT46S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:56:58.468Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T03:56:54.749Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":140,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT209S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T03:56:52.215Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:56:12.308Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:56:12.207Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:56:06.356Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT37S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:56:06.149Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:55:29.060Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT81S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:55:28.959Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 03","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:54:07.848Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT283S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:53:29.979Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T03:53:23.451Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 03","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T03:53:23.314Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 03","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T03:53:11.187Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT9S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T03:53:11.035Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-05-03T03:53:02.652Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":140,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT643S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T03:52:55.471Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:48:46.464Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT570S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:43:05.848Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T03:42:12.916Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:42:12.742Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:42:05.627Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:42:03.202Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 05","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-05-03T03:41:41.845Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":140,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:41:41.801Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 04","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:33:35.400Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT465S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:26:25.409Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 12","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-03T03:18:40.581Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:18:40.414Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:18:35.788Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-03T03:18:31.664Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:18:31.581Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":141,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:11:28.681Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":141,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:11:25.925Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":141,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:11:25.915Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":142,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:04:00.409Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":142,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:03:58.123Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":142,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 1","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-03T03:03:33.794Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":142,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:03:32.714Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":142,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:03:24.683Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":142,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:02:42.597Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":142,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:02:40.028Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":142,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 F12 Problem 1B","problem_set":"1. Summarizing Data","time":"2017-05-03T03:02:33.031Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":142,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T03:02:32.931Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":13,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T02:45:44.051Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":13,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T02:45:39.744Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":13,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T02:45:39.729Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":143,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T02:41:18.226Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":143,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T02:41:14.895Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":143,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T02:41:14.887Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":73,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T01:27:23.804Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":73,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T01:27:05.017Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":73,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T01:27:03.503Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":73,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T01:26:29.852Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":73,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T01:26:26.274Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":73,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T01:26:22.099Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":73,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T01:26:17.952Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":73,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T01:26:17.896Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":144,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 12","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T00:25:49.464Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":144,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT96S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T00:25:45.697Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":144,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T00:24:09.143Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":144,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T00:24:09.090Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":144,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T00:24:04.683Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":144,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 03","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T00:23:58.489Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":144,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T00:23:58.427Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":144,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T00:23:46.786Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":144,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 02","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T00:23:40.640Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":144,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-03T00:23:40.576Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 12","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-03T00:09:10.348Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":145,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT19S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:39:03.639Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:38:44.263Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT11S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 20","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:38:44.156Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 20","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:38:33.483Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT9S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:38:33.366Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:38:24.341Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":145,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT121S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:38:07.113Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:36:06.454Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":145,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT304S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2014 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 15","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:35:52.350Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2014 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 15","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:30:48.698Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":145,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT32S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 12","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:30:38.531Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 12","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:30:06.924Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":145,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT129S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 10","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:29:55.610Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 10","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:27:46.679Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":145,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT620S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:25:32.696Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T23:15:12.829Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T23:15:12.677Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T23:14:41.997Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T23:14:38.895Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T23:14:34.427Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T23:14:24.506Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T23:14:09.818Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T23:14:07.162Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T23:14:03.832Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T23:13:53.572Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T23:13:51.493Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Winter 09 Problem 20","problem_set":"Maxwell's equations","time":"2017-05-02T23:13:48.220Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":145,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T23:13:48.070Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":106,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T21:11:29.482Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":106,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T21:11:29.477Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 4","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:04:01.451Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":3,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT10S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 1","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:03:58.054Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 1","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:03:48.839Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":3,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT9S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 8","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:03:47.178Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 8","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:03:38.506Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 2","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:03:38.392Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 2","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:03:34.476Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT16S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 2","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:03:34.358Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 2","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:03:18.748Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":3,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT62S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 5","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:03:10.836Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 5","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:02:08.232Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":3,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT15S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 7","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:02:04.198Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 7","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:01:49.892Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT8S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 5","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:01:49.782Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 5","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T18:01:41.941Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T18:01:41.740Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T18:01:26.028Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T18:01:26.019Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":146,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT767S","problem":"PB1_088","problem_set":"Measurements and Calculations","time":"2017-05-02T17:49:44.781Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB1_088","problem_set":"Measurements and Calculations","time":"2017-05-02T17:36:57.520Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"PB1_075","problem_set":"Measurements and Calculations","time":"2017-05-02T17:36:57.460Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB1_075","problem_set":"Measurements and Calculations","time":"2017-05-02T17:36:53.458Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T17:36:53.397Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T17:36:50.022Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T17:36:48.184Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T17:36:45.805Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB1_108","problem_set":"Measurements and Calculations","time":"2017-05-02T17:36:44.272Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB1_012","problem_set":"Measurements and Calculations","time":"2017-05-02T17:36:30.855Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":146,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT7S","problem":"PB1_040","problem_set":"Measurements and Calculations","time":"2017-05-02T17:36:18.166Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB1_040","problem_set":"Measurements and Calculations","time":"2017-05-02T17:36:11.767Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T17:36:11.621Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T17:36:07.667Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T17:36:09.392Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T17:36:06.177Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1493737528","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T16:05:53.643Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":147,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PEF_15","problem_set":"Final","time":"2017-05-02T15:59:27.646Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":147,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PEF_15","problem_set":"Final","time":"2017-05-02T15:59:25.069Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":147,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T15:59:25.003Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T15:05:51.958Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T15:05:50.015Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 W14 Problem 5A","problem_set":"1. Summarizing Data","time":"2017-05-02T15:05:28.128Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T15:05:28.090Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":148,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T13:35:46.051Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":148,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T13:35:42.686Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":148,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T13:35:40.618Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":148,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-05-02T13:35:36.094Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":148,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T13:35:36.056Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 Sp13 Problem 11F","problem_set":"1. Summarizing Data","time":"2017-05-02T06:50:30.329Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T06:50:28.910Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T06:50:20.715Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T06:50:12.369Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: EECS 314 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T06:50:10.436Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: EECS 314 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T06:50:07.774Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Thevenin Equivalent Voltage P6","problem_set":"Thevenin Equivalent Voltage","time":"2017-05-02T06:50:00.386Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for EECS 314","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T06:50:00.212Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"EECS 314","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: EECS 314 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T06:49:54.613Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T06:49:52.450Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T06:49:51.023Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T06:24:37.328Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":62,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T06:24:37.323Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":149,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB7_063","problem_set":"Atomic Structure and Periodicity","time":"2017-05-02T04:57:48.392Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":149,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T04:57:48.341Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1493695381","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T04:25:22.285Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 06","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-02T03:58:33.760Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT719S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-02T03:58:33.660Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 235","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 235 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:55:21.095Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 235","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 235 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 17","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T03:55:17.941Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 235","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 235 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:55:16.406Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 235","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 235 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 10","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-05-02T03:55:12.836Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 235","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 235","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:55:11.500Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 235","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 235 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:55:05.487Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:55:00.729Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:59.211Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 5","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T03:54:58.445Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 8","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T03:54:49.927Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":150,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT6S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 2","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T03:54:47.456Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 2","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T03:54:41.936Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:40.184Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:36.477Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:35.045Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:31.851Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:29.377Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 235","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 235 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:23.485Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 235","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 235 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:22.407Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 235","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 235 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:21.354Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 235","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 235 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:20.614Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:13.748Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:54:11.549Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W13 Problem 1E","problem_set":"10. ANOVA: Analysis of Variance","time":"2017-05-02T03:54:10.004Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 20","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-02T03:46:34.519Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W13 Problem 1B","problem_set":"10. ANOVA: Analysis of Variance","time":"2017-05-02T03:41:41.570Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":150,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:41:41.496Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT3418S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-02T03:41:17.902Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":138,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:25:19.253Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":138,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 F12 Problem 1E","problem_set":"1. Summarizing Data","time":"2017-05-02T03:25:04.937Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":138,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:25:04.601Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":138,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:23:16.028Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":138,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:23:01.915Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":138,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T03:23:01.729Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-02T02:44:19.364Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT107S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 3 Spring 11 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-02T02:43:39.829Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 3 Spring 11 Problem 07","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-02T02:41:52.004Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":2,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT40S","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-02T01:59:56.926Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vectors","time":"2017-05-02T01:59:16.351Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T01:59:16.180Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T01:59:04.333Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T01:58:19.452Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 3","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T01:58:11.212Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 5","problem_set":"Chapter 1","time":"2017-05-02T01:58:08.023Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 4 Problem 37","problem_set":"Chapter 4","time":"2017-05-02T01:58:07.671Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 4 Problem 37","problem_set":"Chapter 4","time":"2017-05-02T01:58:01.331Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 5 Problem 8","problem_set":"Chapter 5","time":"2017-05-02T01:58:01.021Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 5 Problem 8","problem_set":"Chapter 5","time":"2017-05-02T01:57:54.224Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 3 Problem 4","problem_set":"Chapter 3","time":"2017-05-02T01:57:53.641Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 3 Problem 4","problem_set":"Chapter 3","time":"2017-05-02T01:57:47.115Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T01:57:46.808Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T01:57:40.919Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T01:57:40.911Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 19","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-02T01:53:25.809Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T01:53:25.798Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T01:29:29.968Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T01:29:29.959Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1493684917","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T01:28:48.107Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":151,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"F12_E1_Q5","problem_set":"Exam 1","time":"2017-05-02T01:19:56.731Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":151,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T01:19:56.701Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T00:28:47.078Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 02","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-02T00:28:37.678Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T00:28:37.665Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":152,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T00:05:32.457Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":152,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-02T00:05:32.448Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":153,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T17:58:50.584Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":153,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T17:58:44.824Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":153,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T17:58:44.781Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":141,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T17:44:24.672Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":141,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T17:43:51.440Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":141,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T17:43:43.908Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":141,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T17:43:35.712Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":141,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T17:43:35.704Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T16:27:41.310Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 23","problem_set":"Scaling","time":"2017-05-01T16:26:41.695Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T16:26:32.180Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T16:26:29.621Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T16:24:32.276Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T16:24:29.075Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T16:24:26.375Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":2,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T16:24:26.204Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":154,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T15:38:15.497Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":154,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T15:38:12.590Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":154,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 W14 Problem 4C","problem_set":"6. Learning about the Difference in Population Proportions","time":"2017-05-01T15:38:09.684Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":154,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T15:38:09.471Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":155,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB14_080","problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","time":"2017-05-01T04:56:12.725Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":155,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T04:56:12.453Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-05-01T02:09:08.882Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-05-01T02:09:08.668Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T18:29:45.768Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T18:29:41.855Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB11_011","problem_set":"Liquids and Solids","time":"2017-04-30T18:29:36.129Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T18:29:35.529Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T12:16:22.796Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 12","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-04-30T12:12:27.970Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT22S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 03","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-04-30T12:12:27.819Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 03","problem_set":"Coulomb's law","time":"2017-04-30T12:12:05.943Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T12:12:05.787Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T12:11:52.299Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T12:11:51.693Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 24","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-30T12:11:35.012Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T12:11:34.864Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T12:11:31.761Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-30T12:11:25.932Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T12:11:25.839Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":159,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T02:58:39.290Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":159,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T02:58:31.203Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":159,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T02:58:31.094Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":160,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 Sp13 Problem 5C","problem_set":"8. Learning about a Population Mean Difference","time":"2017-04-30T01:14:49.362Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":160,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W12 Problem 6J","problem_set":"2. Sampling, Studies, Experiments","time":"2017-04-30T00:23:36.275Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":160,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-30T00:23:35.985Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":161,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W12 Problem 6J","problem_set":"2. Sampling, Studies, Experiments","time":"2017-04-29T23:53:14.471Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":161,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T23:53:14.281Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":162,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 W13 Problem 1A","problem_set":"2. Sampling, Studies, Experiments","time":"2017-04-29T22:27:47.965Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":162,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T22:27:47.875Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":163,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 Sp13 Problem 7D","problem_set":"5. Learning about a Population Proportion","time":"2017-04-29T19:34:45.868Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":163,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T19:34:45.804Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-29T14:08:35.092Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T14:08:34.752Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T14:08:24.349Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T14:08:21.348Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 18","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-29T14:08:19.614Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 05","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-29T14:08:19.170Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 09 Problem 12","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-29T14:07:33.638Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":158,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T14:07:33.574Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":164,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 W12 Problem 5D","problem_set":"7. Learning about a Population Mean","time":"2017-04-29T13:15:14.103Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":164,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T13:15:13.627Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":165,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T05:37:42.593Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":165,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T05:36:11.357Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":165,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T05:35:59.831Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":165,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T05:35:55.693Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":165,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-29T05:35:55.683Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1493411243","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-28T21:28:29.944Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":166,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-28T20:28:28.420Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":166,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-28T20:28:21.699Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":166,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-28T20:27:47.297Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":166,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-28T20:27:45.348Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":166,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-28T20:27:34.275Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":166,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-28T20:27:31.627Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":166,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-28T20:27:26.654Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":166,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 6","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-28T20:27:23.471Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":166,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-28T20:27:23.427Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":151,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"F11_E2_Q07","problem_set":"Exam 1","time":"2017-04-28T04:53:33.291Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":151,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-28T04:53:33.257Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB14_048","problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","time":"2017-04-27T22:16:31.660Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT34S","problem":"PEF_10","problem_set":"Final","time":"2017-04-27T22:16:28.101Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PEF_10","problem_set":"Final","time":"2017-04-27T22:15:53.811Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"PB14_039","problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","time":"2017-04-27T22:15:53.601Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB14_039","problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","time":"2017-04-27T22:15:49.056Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"PB6_063","problem_set":"Chemical Energy","time":"2017-04-27T22:15:48.858Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB6_063","problem_set":"Chemical Energy","time":"2017-04-27T22:15:45.593Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT10S","problem":"F11_E2_Q03","problem_set":"Exam 1","time":"2017-04-27T22:15:40.357Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"F11_E2_Q03","problem_set":"Exam 1","time":"2017-04-27T22:15:30.530Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T22:15:30.065Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T22:15:26.772Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T22:15:15.406Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T22:15:08.852Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T22:15:08.843Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":168,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T22:04:05.815Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":168,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T22:04:05.804Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":169,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T19:47:52.639Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":169,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T19:30:00.500Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":169,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T19:30:00.389Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":170,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T18:20:01.271Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":170,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T18:20:00.943Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":171,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 F12 Problem 1F","problem_set":"1. Summarizing Data","time":"2017-04-27T17:11:37.417Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":171,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W13 Problem 7A","problem_set":"1. Summarizing Data","time":"2017-04-27T17:11:37.350Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":171,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W13 Problem 7A","problem_set":"1. Summarizing Data","time":"2017-04-27T17:11:35.771Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":171,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 W13 Problem 10","problem_set":"2. Sampling, Studies, Experiments","time":"2017-04-27T17:11:35.715Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":171,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 W13 Problem 10","problem_set":"2. Sampling, Studies, Experiments","time":"2017-04-27T17:11:33.392Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":171,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 W13 Problem 5A","problem_set":"2. Sampling, Studies, Experiments","time":"2017-04-27T17:11:33.326Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":171,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 W13 Problem 5A","problem_set":"2. Sampling, Studies, Experiments","time":"2017-04-27T17:11:29.869Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":171,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T17:11:29.711Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":171,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T17:11:22.492Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":171,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 W14 Problem 10C","problem_set":"3. Probability","time":"2017-04-27T17:11:14.274Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":171,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T17:11:14.210Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":172,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB3_066","problem_set":"Stoichiometry","time":"2017-04-27T01:34:46.391Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":172,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-27T01:34:46.320Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":173,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-26T22:49:14.740Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":173,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W14 Problem 2L","problem_set":"11. Regression","time":"2017-04-26T22:49:12.236Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":173,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-26T22:49:12.128Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":174,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 W12 Problem 1A","problem_set":"8. Learning about a Population Mean Difference","time":"2017-04-26T22:36:20.147Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":174,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-26T22:36:20.077Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 W12 Problem 2D","problem_set":"1. Summarizing Data","time":"2017-04-26T19:39:12.852Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-26T19:39:12.682Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-26T19:37:23.357Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 F12 Problem 1F","problem_set":"1. Summarizing Data","time":"2017-04-26T19:37:19.851Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":146,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-26T19:37:19.769Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":175,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-26T01:14:02.604Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":175,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-26T01:13:53.115Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":175,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-26T01:13:48.277Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":175,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-26T01:13:32.467Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":175,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-26T01:13:32.428Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":176,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T22:55:15.663Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":176,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T22:55:15.656Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":177,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB10_093","problem_set":"Molecular Structure and Orbitals","time":"2017-04-25T21:35:53.168Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":177,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T21:35:53.121Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":178,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 07","problem_set":"Angular momentum","time":"2017-04-25T17:30:45.772Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":178,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T17:30:45.748Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":7,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W12 Problem 6C","problem_set":"11. Regression","time":"2017-04-25T15:50:54.491Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":7,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T15:50:54.448Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":179,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W14 Problem 8C","problem_set":"12. Chi-Square Tests","time":"2017-04-25T15:10:20.906Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":179,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T15:10:20.843Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":180,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB15_007","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-25T11:54:40.679Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":180,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T11:54:40.641Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":181,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB7_019","problem_set":"Atomic Structure and Periodicity","time":"2017-04-25T05:24:31.085Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":181,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"PB8_008","problem_set":"Atomic Structure and Periodicity","time":"2017-04-25T05:24:31.006Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":181,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB8_008","problem_set":"Atomic Structure and Periodicity","time":"2017-04-25T05:24:24.141Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":181,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T05:24:24.127Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":169,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T02:33:35.747Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":169,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T02:33:35.666Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":182,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W13 Problem 2A","problem_set":"12. Chi-Square Tests","time":"2017-04-25T01:41:48.417Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":182,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T01:41:48.300Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":183,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T01:22:04.545Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":183,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T01:14:05.683Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 2 Problem 5","problem_set":"Chapter 2","time":"2017-04-25T01:06:07.038Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T01:06:06.840Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T01:05:39.472Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":3,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T01:05:39.464Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":184,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 W14 Problem 12B","problem_set":"7. Learning about a Population Mean","time":"2017-04-25T00:59:05.113Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":184,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-25T00:59:05.066Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":181,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB8_082","problem_set":"Atomic Structure and Periodicity","time":"2017-04-24T23:07:45.448Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":181,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T23:07:45.409Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":185,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T22:49:03.756Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":185,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T22:49:03.744Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":186,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB14_026","problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","time":"2017-04-24T22:17:10.419Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":186,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T22:17:10.312Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":178,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T22:10:09.055Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":187,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PEF_23","problem_set":"Final","time":"2017-04-24T20:47:14.350Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":187,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T20:47:14.281Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":188,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T19:46:52.823Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":188,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T19:46:49.482Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":188,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T19:46:49.473Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"F10_E1_Q25","problem_set":"Exam 2","time":"2017-04-24T19:43:44.969Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT27S","problem":"W13_E1_Q20","problem_set":"Exam 2","time":"2017-04-24T19:43:44.770Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"W13_E1_Q20","problem_set":"Exam 2","time":"2017-04-24T19:43:17.986Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"F12_E1_Q11","problem_set":"Exam 2","time":"2017-04-24T19:43:17.806Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"F12_E1_Q11","problem_set":"Exam 2","time":"2017-04-24T19:43:12.477Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT13S","problem":"F10_E1_Q20","problem_set":"Exam 2","time":"2017-04-24T19:43:12.242Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"F10_E1_Q20","problem_set":"Exam 2","time":"2017-04-24T19:42:59.335Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T19:42:58.851Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T19:42:48.398Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T19:42:44.655Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB15_018","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-24T19:42:42.776Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"PB15_001","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-24T19:42:42.594Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB15_001","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-24T19:42:40.259Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"PB15_029","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-24T19:42:40.066Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB15_029","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-24T19:42:34.229Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT16S","problem":"PB15_005","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-24T19:42:33.963Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB15_005","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-24T19:42:17.620Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T19:42:17.606Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB15_031","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-24T19:42:17.588Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":189,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T19:42:17.525Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":168,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T18:23:13.482Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":168,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T18:22:58.233Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":168,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T18:16:51.356Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":168,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T18:16:23.373Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":168,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W12 Problem 9D","problem_set":"8. Learning about a Population Mean Difference","time":"2017-04-24T18:16:21.731Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":168,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 W12 Problem 1D","problem_set":"8. Learning about a Population Mean Difference","time":"2017-04-24T18:16:13.642Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":168,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T18:16:13.611Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":162,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 W12 Problem 2A","problem_set":"2. Sampling, Studies, Experiments","time":"2017-04-24T17:41:20.175Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":162,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T17:41:20.144Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":173,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam F12 Problem 4D","problem_set":"11. Regression","time":"2017-04-24T15:30:26.713Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":173,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T15:30:26.665Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":183,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T14:17:15.780Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":183,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T14:17:15.771Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":7,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W14 Problem 8A","problem_set":"12. Chi-Square Tests","time":"2017-04-24T03:16:40.080Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":7,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 W13 Problem 1C","problem_set":"9. Learning about the Difference in Population Means","time":"2017-04-24T02:31:44.246Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":7,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T02:31:44.198Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":190,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam F12 Problem 5D","problem_set":"12. Chi-Square Tests","time":"2017-04-24T01:45:05.860Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":190,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T01:45:05.673Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":190,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T01:45:02.904Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":190,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T01:44:57.004Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":190,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T01:44:53.670Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":190,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T01:44:53.484Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":190,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T01:44:37.451Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":190,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T01:44:34.996Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":190,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-24T01:44:34.924Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":157,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT20S","problem":"PB15_032","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-23T21:23:48.883Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB15_032","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-23T21:23:28.942Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":157,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT2S","problem":"PB14_002","problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","time":"2017-04-23T21:23:16.651Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB14_002","problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","time":"2017-04-23T21:23:14.891Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":157,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT5S","problem":"PB14_002","problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","time":"2017-04-23T21:23:13.063Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB14_002","problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","time":"2017-04-23T21:23:08.302Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":157,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT2S","problem":"PB15_019","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:58.704Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB15_019","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:56.626Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":157,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT1S","problem":"PB15_019","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:54.791Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB15_019","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:53.109Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":157,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT2S","problem":"PB15_019","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:50.884Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB15_019","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:48.366Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":157,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT4S","problem":"PB15_029","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:43.628Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB15_029","problem_set":"Acids and Bases","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:39.396Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":157,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT4S","problem":"PB14_046","problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:34.185Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB14_046","problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:30.610Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T21:22:30.398Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T21:22:18.489Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":157,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT2S","problem":"PEF_12","problem_set":"Final","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:04.106Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PEF_12","problem_set":"Final","time":"2017-04-23T21:22:02.137Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":157,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT11S","problem":"PEF_12","problem_set":"Final","time":"2017-04-23T21:21:58.559Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PEF_12","problem_set":"Final","time":"2017-04-23T21:21:47.530Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":157,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T21:21:47.490Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":191,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 F12 Problem 7B","problem_set":"6. Learning about the Difference in Population Proportions","time":"2017-04-23T20:25:35.207Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":191,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T20:25:35.170Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":192,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T20:16:08.789Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":192,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T20:16:08.779Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1492972286","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T19:32:24.096Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":181,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB10_083","problem_set":"Bonding","time":"2017-04-23T18:32:23.880Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":181,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT20S","problem":"PB9_015","problem_set":"Bonding","time":"2017-04-23T18:32:16.063Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":181,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB9_015","problem_set":"Bonding","time":"2017-04-23T18:31:56.531Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":181,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB9_082","problem_set":"Bonding","time":"2017-04-23T18:31:39.401Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":181,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT11S","problem":"PB9_053","problem_set":"Bonding","time":"2017-04-23T18:31:38.000Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":181,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB9_053","problem_set":"Bonding","time":"2017-04-23T18:31:26.255Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":181,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T18:31:26.158Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":193,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T17:53:19.934Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":194,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 12","problem_set":"Magnetic materials","time":"2017-04-23T17:48:45.872Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":194,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T17:48:45.780Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":193,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T17:42:02.218Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":193,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T17:42:02.131Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 03","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-04-23T07:21:24.898Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T07:21:24.830Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T07:21:12.738Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T07:21:07.722Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T07:21:05.651Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T07:21:01.313Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 11","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-23T07:21:01.367Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":196,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W14 Problem 6B","problem_set":"6. Learning about the Difference in Population Proportions","time":"2017-04-23T01:33:52.579Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":196,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T01:33:52.545Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":197,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 F12 Problem 2E","problem_set":"2. Sampling, Studies, Experiments","time":"2017-04-23T00:10:26.457Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":197,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T00:10:26.073Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":198,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T00:05:51.450Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":198,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T00:05:44.990Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":198,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T00:05:39.579Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":198,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-23T00:05:38.565Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":199,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Statistics 250","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T20:44:16.462Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":199,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T20:44:16.420Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 16","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:33.963Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 16","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:33.888Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 16","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:31.757Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 02 Problem 20","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:31.621Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 02 Problem 20","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:29.432Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 20","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:29.371Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 20","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:28.593Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 10","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:28.491Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 10","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:27.434Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 24","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:27.367Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 24","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:26.680Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 13","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:26.603Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 13","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:25.634Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 24","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:25.574Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 24","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:24.475Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:24.405Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:23.032Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 18","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:22.963Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 18","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:20.846Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 22","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:20.720Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 22","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:19.130Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 10","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:19.068Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 10","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:18.155Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:18.091Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:16.729Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 10","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:16.666Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 10","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:15.383Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:15.322Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:13.926Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 13","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:13.859Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 13","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:12.790Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:12.727Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:11.506Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 3","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:11.441Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 3","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:10.133Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 03","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:10.074Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 03","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:09.014Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 19","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:08.847Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 19","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:07.266Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 02 Problem 03","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:07.202Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 02 Problem 03","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:05.467Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 8","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:05.398Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 8","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:03.963Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 10","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:03.887Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 10","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:02.231Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 3","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:02.148Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 3","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:00.804Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 14","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:17:00.744Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 14","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:59.697Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 20","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:59.634Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 20","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:58.441Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 8","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:58.372Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 8","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:56.546Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T20:16:56.479Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T20:16:52.092Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 12","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:50.461Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 11","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:50.395Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 11","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:48.605Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 9","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:48.540Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 9","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:47.223Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 15","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:47.156Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 15","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:45.430Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 02 Problem 20","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:45.366Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 02 Problem 20","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:44.134Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 19","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:44.066Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 19","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:42.868Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 03","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:42.797Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 03","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:40.267Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 9","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:40.202Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 9","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:38.117Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T20:16:37.989Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T20:16:32.444Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-22T20:16:30.365Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":5,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T20:16:30.342Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":200,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T19:53:43.800Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":200,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T19:53:43.667Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Submitted","actor":201,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T15:36:35.594Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":201,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T15:36:35.432Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":202,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT71S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 04","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:56:15.655Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 04","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:55:04.582Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 18","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:55:04.374Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 18","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:55:03.489Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:55:03.194Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:55:02.275Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:55:02.053Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:55:00.882Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:55:00.676Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:59.532Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:59.315Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:58.203Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:57.978Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:57.043Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:56.835Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:55.883Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 19","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:55.687Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 19","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:54.048Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 19","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:53.831Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 19","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:52.277Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT953S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:54:52.048Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:59.805Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:59.598Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:58.284Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 5","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:58.072Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 5","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:56.925Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":202,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:54.928Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:47.332Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 22","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:47.136Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 22","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:46.455Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:46.245Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:45.503Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:45.307Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:44.617Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:44.398Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:43.733Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:43.530Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:42.707Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:42.437Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:41.264Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:41.058Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:39.472Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:39.267Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:38.316Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 FA2010 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:38.096Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 FA2010 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:36.922Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 3","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:36.632Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 3","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:35.674Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:35.456Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:34.535Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:34.332Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:33.575Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:33.371Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:31.973Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:31.767Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:29.991Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":202,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT15S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:21.626Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:06.859Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:06.638Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:05.001Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:04.789Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:03.625Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:03.421Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:00.315Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:38:00.024Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 13","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:58.944Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:58.733Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:57.801Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 20","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:57.593Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 20","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:56.630Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:56.424Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:55.395Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 16","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:55.200Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 16","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:53.155Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 16","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:52.945Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 16","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:50.803Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:50.596Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:49.216Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:48.977Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:46.960Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 11","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:46.741Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 5","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:41.713Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 11","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:43.129Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:42.849Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:41.921Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 5","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:40.726Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:40.510Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:39.501Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:39.297Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:38.216Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 10","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:38.003Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 10","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:36.924Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 10","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:36.721Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 10","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:35.641Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 04","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:35.438Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 04","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:34.329Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:34.117Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:30.685Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:30.477Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:28.649Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 9","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:28.445Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 9","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:26.228Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:26.020Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:22.371Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Winter 04 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:22.163Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Winter 04 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:20.593Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT21S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:37:20.378Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:59.877Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:59.667Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:58.690Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:58.475Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:56.017Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT11S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 03","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:55.799Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 03","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:44.126Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 20","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:43.916Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 20","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:42.672Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:42.469Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:41.298Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:41.094Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:39.524Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:39.302Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:38.023Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:37.813Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:36.449Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:36.242Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:34.960Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:34.761Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:33.510Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 03","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:33.296Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 03","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:32.489Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 18","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:32.290Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 18","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:31.068Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:30.862Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:29.772Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:29.568Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:22.470Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:22.264Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:21.275Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:21.074Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:20.071Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:19.865Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:18.834Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:18.637Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:17.592Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:17.388Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:16.199Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:15.990Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:12.522Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT66S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 16","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:36:12.305Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 16","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:35:06.070Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:35:05.868Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:35:04.663Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:35:04.449Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:35:03.119Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 10","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:35:02.914Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 10","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:35:01.854Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:35:01.579Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:35:00.241Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT47S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:35:00.028Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:13.750Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:13.544Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:11.935Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 07","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:11.720Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 07","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:10.406Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:10.192Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:09.222Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:09.011Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 08","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:07.347Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 22","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:07.148Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 22","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:05.410Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 10","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:05.116Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 10","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:03.863Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:03.654Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:01.954Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:34:01.744Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 17","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:59.042Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:58.846Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 06","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:56.066Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 16","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:55.867Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 16","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:54.624Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 04","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:54.420Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 04","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:53.364Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 5","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:53.155Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 5","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:51.786Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 FA2010 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:51.577Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 FA2010 Problem 12","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:49.108Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T14:33:48.891Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T14:33:28.725Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 12","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-04-22T14:33:23.571Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":202,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T14:33:23.493Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":173,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Final Exam W12 Problem 6A","problem_set":"11. Regression","time":"2017-04-22T13:46:19.149Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":173,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T13:46:19.048Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":203,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 01","problem_set":"Flux and Gauss' law","time":"2017-04-22T03:40:45.060Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":203,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T03:40:45.025Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T02:34:28.117Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-22T02:34:07.708Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 135","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T02:34:07.635Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T02:33:58.647Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T02:33:54.955Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T02:33:52.754Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 4 Problem 35","problem_set":"Chapter 4","time":"2017-04-22T02:33:46.524Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for MCDB 310","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T02:33:46.435Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"MCDB 310","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: MCDB 310 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T02:33:40.407Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T02:33:32.139Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":195,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T02:33:32.081Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":204,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 W13 Problem 9A","problem_set":"6. Learning about the Difference in Population Proportions","time":"2017-04-22T02:16:20.102Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":204,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T02:16:20.092Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":205,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T01:53:18.234Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":205,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T01:53:16.012Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":205,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 W13 Problem 1A","problem_set":"2. Sampling, Studies, Experiments","time":"2017-04-22T01:53:11.882Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":205,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 2 W13 Problem 9A","problem_set":"6. Learning about the Difference in Population Proportions","time":"2017-04-22T01:53:02.790Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":205,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T01:53:02.755Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1492815973","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-22T00:14:41.396Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":206,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T23:17:04.390Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":206,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT171S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 13","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T23:17:00.645Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1492812794","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:16:04.846Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":207,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT24S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:40.828Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:16.490Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:16.423Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 13","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:15.570Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 15","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:15.511Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 15","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:13.702Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT0S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:13.576Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:13.174Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:13.015Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:12.712Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:12.232Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:12.095Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:11.626Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:11.563Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:10.953Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 23","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:10.891Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 23","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:09.964Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":206,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 13","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:09.935Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 10","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:09.893Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":206,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:14:09.849Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 10","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:07.013Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:06.950Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:05.522Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:05.456Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:03.222Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 17","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:03.156Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":206,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:14:03.151Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 17","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:02.050Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:01.987Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:00.092Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 09","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:14:00.027Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 09","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:58.628Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:58.566Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:56.829Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:56.776Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":206,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:55.396Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:53.946Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 23","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:53.890Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":207,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT128S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 22","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:53.200Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 23","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:47.556Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":208,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 16","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:45.272Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 16","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:39.122Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:13:39.041Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:13:03.928Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 01","problem_set":"Forces","time":"2017-04-21T23:13:02.497Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 14","problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","time":"2017-04-21T23:12:58.688Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":208,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:12:58.655Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 22","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T23:11:45.883Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":207,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT57S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T23:11:24.433Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T23:10:27.062Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":207,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT8S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T23:10:25.495Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T23:10:17.909Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":207,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT84S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T23:09:03.367Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 08","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T23:08:57.164Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT268S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 15","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:08:55.407Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T23:07:39.686Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":207,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT49S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T23:07:06.406Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T23:06:17.850Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:06:17.785Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:06:13.818Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:06:13.808Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":210,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 5","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:05:44.410Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":210,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT58S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:05:33.406Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":211,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 5","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T23:04:43.237Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":211,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:04:43.103Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":210,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T23:04:35.269Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":211,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:04:35.183Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":211,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:04:35.167Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":210,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT241S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:04:33.468Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 15","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:04:27.780Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT47S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 08","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T23:04:25.364Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 08","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T23:03:38.246Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 08","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T23:03:38.155Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 08","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T23:03:34.515Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 09 Problem 12","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T23:03:34.431Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 09 Problem 12","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T23:03:22.002Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-21T23:03:21.917Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-21T23:03:16.209Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT33S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 01","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:03:08.615Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 01","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:02:35.450Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT53S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 4","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T23:02:35.357Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":206,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT104S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 24","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T23:02:28.413Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 4","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T23:01:42.234Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT9S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 19","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T23:01:40.776Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 19","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T23:01:31.056Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":206,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 24","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T23:00:44.046Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 13","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T23:00:40.435Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT319S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 03","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:00:38.572Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":210,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T23:00:32.894Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":210,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T23:00:32.810Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":206,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT105S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 22","problem_set":"Radiation energy and momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:56:49.596Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 03","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:55:19.102Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT238S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 18","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T22:55:17.292Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":206,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 22","problem_set":"Radiation energy and momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:55:04.316Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":206,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT269S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:54:58.316Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":212,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT211S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:53:31.803Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1492811176","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:53:09.667Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 18","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T22:51:19.330Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT130S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 3","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:51:17.586Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":210,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:50:47.431Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":210,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:50:38.142Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":210,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:50:38.134Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":206,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:50:29.028Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":206,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:50:28.969Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":206,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:50:25.974Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":206,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:50:25.965Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1492811408","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:50:20.583Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":212,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:50:00.913Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":212,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT244S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 6","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:49:58.009Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 3","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:49:07.524Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT119S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:48:37.465Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 09 Problem 14","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:47:55.596Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:47:41.462Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":214,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT14S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:47:39.600Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":213,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT33S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 09 Problem 18","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:47:26.318Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:47:25.362Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":214,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 19","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:47:19.051Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 19","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:47:07.177Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Final Exam Problem 16","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T22:47:07.001Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Final Exam Problem 16","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T22:47:02.938Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:47:02.910Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 09 Problem 18","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:46:53.923Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT16S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 7","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:46:53.764Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:46:38.599Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT232S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:46:38.511Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 7","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:46:37.161Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":213,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT25S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 21","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:46:32.526Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 21","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:46:07.962Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":213,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT26S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 03","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:46:01.823Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":212,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 6","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:45:53.930Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":212,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:45:53.825Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":212,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:45:47.456Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":212,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 20","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:45:44.645Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":212,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:45:44.601Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 03","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:45:35.317Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 9","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:45:35.204Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T22:45:34.918Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 9","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:45:32.497Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT10S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 19","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:45:32.378Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 19","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:45:22.141Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:45:21.986Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":215,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT193S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 14","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:45:21.274Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:45:19.396Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":213,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:45:19.386Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1492798724","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:44:18.475Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 08","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:44:02.165Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":216,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT16S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 02","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:55.105Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:47.309Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT8S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:47.190Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:39.551Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 02","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:39.357Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":216,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT29S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 24","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:37.387Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":217,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT11S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:36.715Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:25.565Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT11S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:25.470Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:14.809Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":217,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT94S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 23","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:11.738Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 24","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:08.090Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 16","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:07.982Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 16","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:04.124Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 09 Problem 03","problem_set":"Rolling motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:43:04.017Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 09 Problem 03","problem_set":"Rolling motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:42:57.180Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":216,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT23S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 16","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:42:51.984Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:42:46.387Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT360S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 20","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T22:42:46.299Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_TimedOut","actor":1,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"session - 1492809035","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:42:29.372Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 16","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:42:28.417Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":216,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 10","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:42:25.724Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 10","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:42:19.827Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":216,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT19S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 09","problem_set":"Rolling motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:42:17.279Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 14","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:42:08.226Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":215,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT297S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 10","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:41:59.520Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 09","problem_set":"Rolling motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:41:58.151Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":216,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT30S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:41:56.260Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 23","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:41:37.389Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:41:26.939Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:41:26.849Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":217,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT77S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:41:26.328Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 10","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:41:24.151Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT61S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T22:41:21.324Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:41:20.589Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 14","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T22:40:20.444Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT9S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 14","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:40:20.320Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 14","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:40:11.191Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT13S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 02 Problem 06","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:40:11.065Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:40:09.966Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT10S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:40:09.885Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:59.514Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:39:59.098Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":216,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:39:59.090Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 02 Problem 06","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:58.281Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 15","problem_set":"Mechanical energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:52.967Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":217,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT139S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:47.940Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 15","problem_set":"Mechanical energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:40.286Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 7","problem_set":"2D/3D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:40.107Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 7","problem_set":"2D/3D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:34.371Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 20","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:34.223Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 20","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:27.505Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT20S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 02 Problem 08","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:25.077Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 02 Problem 08","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:05.212Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 15","problem_set":"2D/3D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:05.094Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 15","problem_set":"2D/3D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:39:00.369Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT27S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:48.378Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:28.076Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:21.228Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:21.083Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:17.759Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:17.650Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:10.743Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 18","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:10.633Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 18","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:05.948Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT32S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 19","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:03.868Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 10","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:02.892Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":217,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT100S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:37:02.448Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":215,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT118S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 19","problem_set":"Rolling motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:36:55.872Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 20","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T22:36:46.947Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT87S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:36:43.241Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 19","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:36:31.361Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 12","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T22:36:31.225Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 12","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T22:36:26.608Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 19","problem_set":"Angular momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:36:26.493Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 19","problem_set":"Angular momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:36:20.201Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":218,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT151S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 5","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:36:14.882Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT147S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:35:55.834Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:35:22.105Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:35:22.016Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:35:19.379Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 08","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:35:19.300Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 08","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:35:17.357Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT126S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 17","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:35:17.251Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:35:16.974Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT168S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:34:58.528Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 19","problem_set":"Rolling motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:34:57.247Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":215,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT48S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 13","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:34:25.491Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 5","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:33:43.139Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT78S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:33:43.078Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 13","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:33:37.248Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 15","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:33:28.144Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT73S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 12","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:33:15.614Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 17","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:33:11.589Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 23","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:33:11.504Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 23","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:33:06.088Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:33:05.999Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:32:58.406Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT13S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:32:58.304Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":215,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT127S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 20","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:32:57.920Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:32:45.403Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT26S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 01","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:32:28.313Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:32:25.728Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT32S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 17","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:32:25.663Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":217,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT33S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:32:16.229Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:32:10.662Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 01","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:32:02.214Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 12","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:32:02.089Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 2 Winter 08 Problem 10","problem_set":"Current, resistance, and power","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:59.589Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT48S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 06","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:56.561Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 17","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:53.838Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 2 Winter 08 Problem 10","problem_set":"Current, resistance, and power","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:53.543Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":218,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:51.548Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:44.592Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:43.160Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:42.994Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":218,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT20S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 13","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:41.845Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:36.905Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:36.809Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:29.812Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":217,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT41S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:23.296Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 13","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:21.567Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":218,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:18.557Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:12.227Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT57S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 07","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:12.159Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 06","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:31:08.977Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 20","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:30:50.123Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:30:42.874Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT45S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:30:42.773Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":215,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT116S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 06","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T22:30:32.570Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 07","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:30:15.932Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:29:57.070Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT16S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 24","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:29:56.975Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 24","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:29:40.972Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":217,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT59S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:29:38.262Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT256S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 5","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:29:05.950Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":218,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT123S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:28:41.072Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:28:39.633Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 06","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T22:28:35.994Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":217,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT95S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 19","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:28:35.987Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:28:35.858Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:28:33.769Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 19","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:27:00.954Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT80S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:27:00.862Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 04","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:26:43.640Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:26:38.183Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":215,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT24S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 17","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:26:34.176Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 17","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:26:10.339Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":218,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT27S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 02","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:26:06.688Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:25:40.044Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT45S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 21","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:25:39.956Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 02","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:25:39.028Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 21","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:54.263Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT58S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:54.145Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 5","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:49.387Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":209,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT179S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 07","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:47.187Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":215,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT104S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 14","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:31.899Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:29.760Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 24","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:29.642Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 24","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:28.582Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT1S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:28.521Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:27.184Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:27.114Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:25.812Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 24","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:25.654Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 24","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:23.025Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:20.994Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:17.797Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT2S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:17.699Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:15.985Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:15.926Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:11.949Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:11.876Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:08.449Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 22","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:24:05.470Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 22","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:59.837Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:56.905Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT58S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:56.823Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":221,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 16","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:54.367Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":221,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT24S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 21","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:49.823Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT15S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 22","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:42.748Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 22","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:27.290Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":221,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 21","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:25.376Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:25.350Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":221,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:22.657Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:18.631Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":221,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:16.751Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 13","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:15.578Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":221,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT8S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 19","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:14.974Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 13","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:08.501Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":221,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 19","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:06.497Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":221,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT8S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 16","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:23:04.195Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:58.588Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":221,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 16","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:56.550Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":221,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 18","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:54.898Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":221,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 18","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:48.013Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 14","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:47.285Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":221,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT9S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 20","problem_set":"2D/3D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:46.258Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":215,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT66S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 18","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:44.727Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":221,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 20","problem_set":"2D/3D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:37.495Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":221,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT14S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 24","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:35.445Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":221,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 24","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:21.517Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT71S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 13","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:21.031Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":221,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT13S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 04","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:19.861Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":221,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 04","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:06.801Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":221,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 09","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T22:22:04.630Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":221,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 09","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T22:21:52.604Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":221,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:21:52.570Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 07","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:21:48.263Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:21:48.157Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 18","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:21:38.818Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT38S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 05 Problem 10","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T22:21:38.668Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 13","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:21:09.430Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT48S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:21:06.628Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:21:01.131Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 05 Problem 10","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T22:21:00.049Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":215,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT81S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Winter 04 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T22:20:57.977Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","time":"2017-04-21T22:20:43.768Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":209,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:20:43.734Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:20:18.606Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT13S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:20:14.854Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":218,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT61S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 03","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:20:03.608Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:20:01.811Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT27S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:20:01.701Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Winter 04 Problem 05","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T22:19:36.982Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:19:36.838Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:19:34.569Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:19:34.084Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":215,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:19:34.077Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":222,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 08","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:19:19.599Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 03","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:19:02.660Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:19:02.606Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:18:59.121Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:18:59.110Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT158S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:18:49.921Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:16:11.784Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":223,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT37S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 12","problem_set":"AC circuits","time":"2017-04-21T22:16:03.478Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:15:54.503Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 04","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:15:54.430Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 04","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:15:50.866Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT9S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 12","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:15:50.796Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":217,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT78S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:15:46.924Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:15:44.436Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:15:42.677Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 12","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:15:41.682Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"F11_E2_Q06","problem_set":"Exam 1","time":"2017-04-21T22:15:33.204Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:15:33.154Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:15:30.892Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"F11_E2_Q05","problem_set":"Exam 1","time":"2017-04-21T22:15:29.655Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:15:29.582Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":223,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 12","problem_set":"AC circuits","time":"2017-04-21T22:15:26.223Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:15:25.029Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"PB3_116","problem_set":"Stoichiometry","time":"2017-04-21T22:15:22.781Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Chemistry 130","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:15:22.727Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:15:08.086Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:15:05.382Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT47S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 481 Midterm 1 Fall 2011 Problem 03","problem_set":"Mechanical energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:15:05.274Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":224,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT23S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 04","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:14:55.230Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 04","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:14:32.242Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT22S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 04","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:14:32.174Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:14:28.751Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:14:28.648Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 135","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 135 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:14:28.229Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:14:22.494Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:14:22.344Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Statistics 250 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:14:19.360Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 481 Midterm 1 Fall 2011 Problem 03","problem_set":"Mechanical energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:14:18.613Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Stats 250 Exam 1 Sp13 Problem 1A","problem_set":"4. Random Variables","time":"2017-04-21T22:14:17.341Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":225,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Statistics 250","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:14:17.332Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT17S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 16","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:14:13.691Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 04","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:14:10.747Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":224,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT23S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 08","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:14:07.818Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 22","problem_set":"Radiation energy and momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:59.283Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:13:59.073Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 16","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:56.216Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:56.112Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 13","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:53.411Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT24S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 15","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:53.304Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":223,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT34S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 20","problem_set":"Maxwell's equations","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:49.013Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 08","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:44.035Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT27S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 04","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:43.968Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:13:40.690Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 15","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:29.050Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT62S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 06","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:20.513Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 04","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:16.779Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:13:16.685Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":223,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 20","problem_set":"Maxwell's equations","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:14.956Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":223,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3086S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 17","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:13:14.874Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":223,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:13:14.861Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":222,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT47S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 22","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:12:55.231Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:12:48.560Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":224,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:12:48.551Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 06","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T22:12:18.228Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT13S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 18","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:12:18.126Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":222,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 22","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:12:08.544Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 18","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:12:05.703Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 08","problem_set":"Electric potential","time":"2017-04-21T22:11:51.575Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:11:51.340Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT106S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 20","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:11:46.553Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:11:37.705Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","time":"2017-04-21T22:11:34.215Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":226,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT354S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 04","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:11:32.019Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:11:13.921Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:11:11.996Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 2 Winter 06 Problem 11","problem_set":"Electric potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T22:11:09.049Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":217,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:11:09.030Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT98S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:10:16.606Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 20","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:10:00.315Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT20S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 18","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:09:55.775Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 18","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:09:35.575Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT16S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 04","problem_set":"Angular momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:09:33.425Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":227,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT521S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:09:20.468Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":228,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:09:18.717Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 04","problem_set":"Angular momentum","time":"2017-04-21T22:09:17.293Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT51S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 18","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T22:09:10.806Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":228,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT12S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 09","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:08:59.756Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 03","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:08:52.906Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":228,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 09","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:08:47.009Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T22:08:38.774Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT38S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:08:28.331Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 18","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T22:08:19.011Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":218,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT51S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 09","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:08:15.419Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":229,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 20","problem_set":"Forces","time":"2017-04-21T22:08:01.789Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:07:50.425Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT72S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:07:48.060Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT223S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 18","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:07:39.588Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 09","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:07:24.277Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":230,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:06:53.878Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":230,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 16","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T22:06:45.657Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":218,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT13S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:06:44.269Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":228,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT135S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:06:43.825Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":229,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT305S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:06:39.909Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":230,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 17","problem_set":"2D/3D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:06:37.996Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:06:36.439Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:06:31.276Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 09","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:06:29.896Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":218,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT122S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:06:13.208Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT1558S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T22:05:58.515Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 04","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T22:05:37.386Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":226,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT442S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:05:35.600Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":231,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:05:16.761Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":228,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:04:28.756Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":228,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:04:28.727Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:04:11.399Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:04:10.954Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:04:00.572Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 18","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:03:56.919Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Chemistry 130 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:03:52.634Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":218,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Chemistry 130","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T22:03:52.625Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":232,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 FA2010 Problem 17","problem_set":"Forces","time":"2017-04-21T22:01:39.953Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":232,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT935S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 06","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:01:39.857Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":229,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 17","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-04-21T22:01:34.211Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":229,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT102S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 08","problem_set":"Collisions","time":"2017-04-21T22:01:11.865Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":230,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT93S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 16","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T22:01:08.032Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 15","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:01:01.798Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT17S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 15","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:01:01.671Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 15","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T22:00:44.314Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":227,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T22:00:39.491Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":233,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT276S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 6","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T22:00:35.893Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":222,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT95S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 17","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:59:50.781Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":227,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT321S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 10","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:59:37.406Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":230,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 16","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T21:59:35.138Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":229,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 08","problem_set":"Collisions","time":"2017-04-21T21:59:29.314Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":229,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT254S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 18","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T21:59:24.648Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 01","problem_set":"Forces","time":"2017-04-21T21:58:18.783Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 02","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T21:58:18.678Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 02","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T21:58:15.362Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":222,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 17","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:58:15.089Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":156,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT215S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 13","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:58:13.832Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T21:58:13.748Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT54S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 08","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:58:13.643Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":222,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT985S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:58:13.218Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT38S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","time":"2017-04-21T21:57:50.857Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":230,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT110S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 13","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T21:57:35.670Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 08","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:57:19.238Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","time":"2017-04-21T21:57:12.330Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":226,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT224S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:57:00.887Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT38S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 17","problem_set":"Mechanical energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:56:47.766Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 17","problem_set":"Mechanical energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:56:09.666Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 14","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T21:56:07.111Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 14","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T21:56:01.120Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 08","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:56:01.021Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 6","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:59.443Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 20","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:59.351Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 08","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:58.284Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT133S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:58.188Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 20","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:56.355Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":233,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT1140S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 19","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:54.683Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":234,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT29S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 06","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:54.002Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":230,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 13","problem_set":"Static equilibrium","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:45.740Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 15","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:26.748Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT30S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:26.629Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":234,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 06","problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:24.431Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":234,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT202S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 03","problem_set":"Forces","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:20.038Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":229,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 18","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:10.942Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":230,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT335S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 13","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:55:09.022Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:54:56.425Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:54:56.293Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:54:52.965Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT661S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:54:52.843Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 13","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:54:38.003Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT15S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 15","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T21:54:37.903Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 15","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T21:54:22.076Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":156,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT129S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 05 Problem 10","problem_set":"Forces","time":"2017-04-21T21:54:20.149Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":227,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 10","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:54:16.635Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":227,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:54:16.565Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T21:53:45.199Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT18S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 8","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:53:45.097Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 8","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:53:27.042Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT30S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 23","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:53:25.030Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":227,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:53:24.587Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 11","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:53:16.221Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 11","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T21:53:10.405Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":226,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT464S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 11","problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","time":"2017-04-21T21:53:08.860Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:53:08.516Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":207,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT54S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:53:07.083Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 23","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:52:55.880Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":236,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT789S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:52:49.553Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":227,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT458S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 09","problem_set":"Collisions","time":"2017-04-21T21:52:27.711Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT125S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:52:19.086Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:52:13.631Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 05 Problem 10","problem_set":"Forces","time":"2017-04-21T21:52:11.106Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 20","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T21:52:11.000Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 20","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T21:52:07.588Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":207,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT152S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:52:06.554Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":156,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT28S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 07","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:52:05.944Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":234,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 03","problem_set":"Forces","time":"2017-04-21T21:51:57.611Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":234,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT143S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:51:53.547Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 07","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:51:37.371Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":237,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:51:18.133Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":237,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT30S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:50:53.376Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":237,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:50:23.792Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":238,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:50:17.681Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":167,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:50:14.877Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":238,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:50:12.064Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":237,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT26S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Final Exam Problem 20","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:50:10.625Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":238,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall '05 Problem 18","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:50:08.117Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":238,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:50:08.098Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":231,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 4","problem_set":"Forces","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:49.874Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":237,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Final Exam Problem 20","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:44.584Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":231,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT208S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:41.431Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":229,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT361S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 8","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:39.328Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:34.963Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":230,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 13","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:34.496Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":234,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:30.263Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":207,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT26S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:19.867Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":234,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT74S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 21","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:19.057Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":230,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT106S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:15.538Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":167,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT1876S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 21","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:14.030Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT10S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 08","problem_set":"RC circuits","time":"2017-04-21T21:49:01.426Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:48:53.298Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 08","problem_set":"RC circuits","time":"2017-04-21T21:48:51.986Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":207,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT140S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:48:51.202Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT15S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 2 Winter 08 Problem 07","problem_set":"Current, resistance, and power","time":"2017-04-21T21:48:49.260Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 2 Winter 08 Problem 07","problem_set":"Current, resistance, and power","time":"2017-04-21T21:48:34.228Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT145S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 20","problem_set":"Flux and Gauss' law","time":"2017-04-21T21:48:31.578Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":234,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 21","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:48:05.345Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":234,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT10S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 20","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:47:57.455Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":234,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 20","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:47:47.560Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":234,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT508S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T21:47:36.071Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":230,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:47:29.480Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":230,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT222S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 9","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T21:47:28.174Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":156,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT364S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 14","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T21:47:04.031Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":239,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT32S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 09","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:46:52.537Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:46:31.699Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:46:31.631Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:46:20.029Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":239,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 09","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:46:20.924Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:46:16.648Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":207,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 18","problem_set":"AC circuits","time":"2017-04-21T21:46:16.661Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":231,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:46:13.473Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":231,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:46:13.442Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 20","problem_set":"Flux and Gauss' law","time":"2017-04-21T21:46:06.886Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":232,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 06","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T21:46:04.872Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":232,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:46:04.781Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT20S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 15","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:46:03.703Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":239,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT72S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 06","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:46:00.925Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 15","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:45:43.169Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 11","problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","time":"2017-04-21T21:45:24.546Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":226,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT36S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 09 Problem 13","problem_set":"Mechanical energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:45:23.359Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":227,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 09","problem_set":"Collisions","time":"2017-04-21T21:44:49.954Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":239,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 06","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:44:48.468Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 09 Problem 13","problem_set":"Mechanical energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:44:47.944Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":226,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT233S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:44:46.469Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":232,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:44:39.493Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":232,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:44:39.485Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":239,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT34S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 13","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:44:33.914Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 12","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T21:44:16.774Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":214,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT16S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 3","problem_set":"Orbits / Kepler's laws","time":"2017-04-21T21:44:15.455Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":227,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT86S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 19","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T21:44:08.981Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":239,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 13","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:43:59.865Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 3","problem_set":"Orbits / Kepler's laws","time":"2017-04-21T21:43:59.631Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":214,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT186S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 03","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:43:57.622Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:43:51.490Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":235,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT420S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T21:43:50.019Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":230,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 9","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T21:43:46.736Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":230,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT126S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 02","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:43:41.439Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":229,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 8","problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:43:38.546Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":229,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT264S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 08","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:43:37.213Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT83S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:43:12.939Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":239,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT96S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 01","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:43:07.735Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":227,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 19","problem_set":"Moment of inertia","time":"2017-04-21T21:42:42.006Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":227,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 10","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T21:42:41.933Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":227,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 10","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T21:42:34.529Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":240,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:42:28.949Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":240,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT93S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:42:27.165Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:41:49.141Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":222,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:41:48.608Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":227,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT266S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 14","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T21:41:46.211Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT289S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 11","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-04-21T21:41:46.052Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":230,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 02","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:41:35.268Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":230,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:41:35.167Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":239,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 01","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:41:31.952Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":239,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:41:31.307Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":239,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:41:14.566Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":239,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:41:14.556Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 14","problem_set":"1D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:59.169Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":156,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT70S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 5","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:57.891Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":240,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:54.002Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:53.800Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":222,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT228S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 16","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:52.272Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":226,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT260S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 01","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:52.222Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 03","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:51.896Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":240,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT48S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:51.667Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":214,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT64S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:50.564Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":241,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT110S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 08","problem_set":"Electric potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:34.539Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":240,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:03.921Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":240,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT22S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:02.543Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:40:00.583Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT43S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:58.522Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 5","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:47.876Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":156,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT51S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 06","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:46.579Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:46.502Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":214,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT26S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 20","problem_set":"Rolling motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:45.199Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":236,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:40.766Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":236,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT27S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 17","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:40.661Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":240,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:40.033Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":240,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT884S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:36.948Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 20","problem_set":"Rolling motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:19.091Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:15.942Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":229,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 08","problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:13.081Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":236,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 17","problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:13.024Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":236,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:39:12.989Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":234,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:08.920Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":214,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT40S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 05","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:02.767Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":229,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT28S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T21:39:00.442Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 06","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:38:55.637Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":156,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT65S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T21:38:54.328Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":241,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 08","problem_set":"Electric potential energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:38:44.738Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":241,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT124S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 20","problem_set":"Electric dipoles","time":"2017-04-21T21:38:41.229Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":229,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T21:38:32.780Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":229,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:38:32.668Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 05","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T21:38:22.478Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":242,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:37:51.866Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 19","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T21:37:49.030Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":156,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT400S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T21:37:47.303Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":242,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 02 Problem 11","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T21:37:32.345Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":234,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT75S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 01","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:37:30.117Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":227,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 14","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T21:37:20.029Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":214,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT153S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 21","problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","time":"2017-04-21T21:37:06.902Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":222,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 16","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:37:04.396Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":222,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT67S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 07","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:37:01.929Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT173S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:37:00.199Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 11","problem_set":"Electric fields","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:57.549Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 19","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:54.542Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 10","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:54.454Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:49.319Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 10","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:48.456Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 06","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:48.320Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 06","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:44.384Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 04","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:44.298Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 04","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:40.570Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":241,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 20","problem_set":"Electric dipoles","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:37.952Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":235,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT45S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 19","problem_set":"Rolling motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:37.226Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":241,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT126S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 24","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:32.619Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 01","problem_set":"Newton's laws","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:32.522Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":226,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT336S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 02 Problem 19","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:31.485Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":234,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 01","problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:15.336Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":234,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 140","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:36:15.233Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":234,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 140 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:36:10.603Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":234,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:36:10.596Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":233,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT72S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 21","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:36:06.293Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":222,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 07","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:35:54.436Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 19","problem_set":"Rolling motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:35:52.609Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":235,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT7S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:35:51.034Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":222,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT2011S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 09","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:35:49.943Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT16S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Winter 06 Problem 19","problem_set":"Capacitance","time":"2017-04-21T21:35:45.002Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Periodic motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:35:44.972Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Winter 06 Problem 19","problem_set":"Capacitance","time":"2017-04-21T21:35:28.009Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT26S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 23","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:35:24.855Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 23","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:58.532Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 21","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:54.130Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT21S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 09","problem_set":"Electric dipoles","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:51.314Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":233,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 16","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:42.023Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 16","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:36.133Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:36.040Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 21","problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:33.754Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 09","problem_set":"Electric dipoles","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:30.180Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:30.162Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 17","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:30.040Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":214,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT338S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:28.109Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 17","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:27.050Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT5S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 03","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:26.963Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT69S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 07","problem_set":"Transformers","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:26.567Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":241,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 24","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:26.133Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":235,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT92S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:23.063Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 03","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:21.149Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":241,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT178S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Electric potential","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:20.764Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":233,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT102S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 12","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:13.237Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:07.086Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT41S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 01","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:34:04.011Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":242,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT139S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 07","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T21:33:36.623Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 01","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:33:22.306Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT23S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 23","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:33:19.434Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 07","problem_set":"Transformers","time":"2017-04-21T21:33:17.968Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":219,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT15S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:33:06.488Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 23","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:32:56.354Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT74S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 24","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:32:53.657Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:32:51.503Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Linear momentum","time":"2017-04-21T21:32:51.422Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:32:51.424Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":235,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT162S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 10","problem_set":"Mechanical energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:32:49.648Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":237,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT62S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:32:36.303Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:32:34.569Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":233,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 12","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:32:31.609Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Course List","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:32:29.691Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":219,"answerCorrect":null,"class":null,"correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:32:29.649Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 24","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:31:39.039Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT128S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:31:35.739Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":237,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:31:34.386Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":241,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 16","problem_set":"Electric potential","time":"2017-04-21T21:31:22.793Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":242,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 07","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T21:31:17.308Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 11","problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T21:31:06.996Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":156,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT80S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 09 Problem 11","problem_set":"Collisions","time":"2017-04-21T21:31:05.411Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":241,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT83S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Winter 06 Problem 05","problem_set":"Ampere's law","time":"2017-04-21T21:31:03.974Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 02 Problem 19","problem_set":"Circular motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:30:55.860Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":226,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT247S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 08","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:30:54.307Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 10","problem_set":"Mechanical energy","time":"2017-04-21T21:30:07.455Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:30:07.315Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:30:04.647Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT4S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Forces","time":"2017-04-21T21:30:04.495Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":237,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT99S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 17","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:30:00.780Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Forces","time":"2017-04-21T21:30:00.470Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Winter 04 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T21:30:00.341Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Winter 04 Problem 10","problem_set":"Vector algebra","time":"2017-04-21T21:29:57.122Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 09 Problem 11","problem_set":"Collisions","time":"2017-04-21T21:29:45.571Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":156,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT181S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Final Exam Problem 9","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:29:44.031Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":241,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Winter 06 Problem 05","problem_set":"Ampere's law","time":"2017-04-21T21:29:40.543Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":241,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"3","duration":"PT132S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 12","problem_set":"Transformers","time":"2017-04-21T21:29:36.616Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:29:27.359Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":235,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT182S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 9","problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","time":"2017-04-21T21:29:26.779Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"4","duration":"PT48S","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:29:24.912Z","value":"4"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 20","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T21:28:50.458Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT39S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T21:28:50.337Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 21","problem_set":"Polarization","time":"2017-04-21T21:28:36.926Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":237,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 17","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:28:21.684Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":237,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT128S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:28:13.371Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":214,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","problem_set":"Stress and strain","time":"2017-04-21T21:28:11.078Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":214,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT302S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:28:05.858Z","value":"3"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":220,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT82S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:28:05.575Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":241,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 12","problem_set":"Transformers","time":"2017-04-21T21:27:24.369Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":241,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT67S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 11","problem_set":"Electric potential","time":"2017-04-21T21:27:10.911Z","value":"1"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 08","problem_set":"Relative motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:47.108Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT270S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 11","problem_set":"Rolling motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:43.891Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":156,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Final Exam Problem 9","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:43.988Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 21","problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:43.829Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:26:43.774Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":226,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 02 Problem 15","problem_set":"2D/3D kinematics","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:37.914Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":226,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT184S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Final Exam Problem 9","problem_set":"Mechanical waves","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:36.401Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentEvent_Reset","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Topics View for Physics 240","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:26:30.786Z","value":null},
{"action":"NavigationEvent_NavigatedTo","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"Selections: Physics 240 Topics","problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:26:26.300Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 9","problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:24.759Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT34S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 03","problem_set":"Collisions","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:24.646Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","problem_set":"Impedance and reactance","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:08.571Z","value":null},
{"action":"SessionEvent_LoggedIn","actor":220,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":null,"problem_set":null,"time":"2017-04-21T21:26:08.558Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":237,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 05","problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:05.470Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":242,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT355S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 04","problem_set":"Center of mass","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:04.235Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":241,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 11","problem_set":"Electric potential","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:03.063Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":237,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"5","duration":"PT22S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 19","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:01.740Z","value":"5"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":241,"answerCorrect":"true","class":"Physics 240","correctAnswer":"2","duration":"PT57S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 12","problem_set":"Ampere's law","time":"2017-04-21T21:26:00.458Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 03","problem_set":"Collisions","time":"2017-04-21T21:25:50.422Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Completed","actor":235,"answerCorrect":"false","class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":"1","duration":"PT8S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 12","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:25:48.700Z","value":"2"},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 12","problem_set":"Sound","time":"2017-04-21T21:25:40.487Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT3S","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:25:40.359Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":237,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 19","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:25:39.733Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","time":"2017-04-21T21:25:37.143Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Skipped","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":"PT6S","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 FA2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:25:37.040Z","value":null},
{"action":"AssessmentItemEvent_Started","actor":235,"answerCorrect":null,"class":"Physics 140","correctAnswer":null,"duration":null,"problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 FA2010 Problem 6","problem_set":"Projectile motion","time":"2017-04-21T21:25:31.407Z","value":null}]